bladguard Oh wow Good afternoon How are
bladguard О ничего себе Добрый день Как
you some blogger probably yes
дела у тебя какой-то блогер наверное да
I'm not talking
я нет
about nifigas Why moronic because it is
о нифигасе Почему по дебильному потому
visible in honor of the mountainous Ukrainians
что видно в честь горных украинцев
who dug the Black Sea, I
которые выкопали Черное море вот
wonder if you saw this story that
интересно ты же видел эту историю что у
you have a scandal like among bloggers about
вас скандал типа среди блогеров про
theft  donations
воровство донатов
solution of donations Yes, the
раствор донатов Да что
blogger to get up the country said that this
блогер вставать страна сказал что вот
is Hell's Roulette
это Адская Рулетка
for donations for the military bought himself a house and
на донаты для военных купил себе дом и
Porsche really showed here to be
Porsche тут реально показывал чтобы
so sure that he bought a tun with this money Well,
так уверен что на эти деньги тун купил
he’s sure Yes, there’s yours,
Ну вот он уверен Да вот ваша
look at your blogger from Krasnodar
есть вот смотри ваш блогер из Краснодара
he  counted In short, the dude doesn’t
он посчитал Короче что-то чувак нигде не
work anywhere yes he collected for the armed
работает да он собирал на вооруженные
forces counted how much he collected yes And
силы посчитал сколько он собрал да И
how much he collected for himself here the dude bought
сколько на себя собирал тут чувак купил
a port to the house And how he calculated This is how he
порт в дом А как он посчитал Вот так
watched the fees Go to the channel there is a
смотрел сборы Идите на канал вот есть
second side What do you think  which one
вторая сторона Вот вы как считаете кто
of them is a pizdabol Get up the country or
из них [__] Вставай страна или
I can’t judge about I don’t understand, you
я не могу судить по поводу не разбираюсь
understand,
понимаешь
they already said their muzzles there they say that
сказал они уже морды там говорят что вот
now Dmitry Donskoy said that she
вот Дмитрий не Донской говорил что она
hits the face like this Get up the country
бьёт морду типа этому Вставай стране
Dmitry
Дмитрий
here he don’t know why you burned him too
вот он не знаю почему ты его тоже
that it’s Get up  the country said
подгорело что это Вставай страна сказал
that, look, bloggers should make
что смотрите блогеры должны делать
reports on fees yes, like they bought the Czech Republic, yes, and this is
отчеты о сборах да типа Чехии купили да
Nord
а это Северный
Stream, then [ __ ] off, in short, we started
поток значит Пошел нахуй короче начали
matyuk, like something, we won’t do something to
матюка типа что-то не будем делать
sort out the situation anyway, from the other
разобраться за ситуации всё равно с той
side, it’s like this is what you’re just
стороны мне как бы это то что вы там
catching up there
нагоняете
we don’t understand
просто мы такие не разбираюсь
you, what are you doing there collecting a soldier
вы что же какие-то там собираете солдата
Yes, but it turns out that those who don’t
делаете Да а получается что те кто не
do it are rats like that Well,
делают это они крысы так
I wouldn’t say well, wait, look,
Ну я бы не сказал ну подожди смотри
here you have a type of report in Ukraine
вот у вас есть типа вид отчет на Украине
which Avito you have a resource where
какой Avito есть вас ресурс где между
you sell to each other to this site Where
собой продаете к этой площадка Где
you post yours, let’s say you want to
выкладываете свои допустим ты хочешь
sell Well, somehow
продать Ну вот как-то с него чек
you’ll get a check from it But I don’t look For example,
получишь А я не смотри Вот например я
when I collect these donations I translate the
когда собираю эти донаты Я перевожу
translation in full, there is a foundation in my city, a
полностью перевод вот есть в моём городе
charitable foundation, volunteers
благотворительный фонд волонтёры
divided, they don’t work  the first year they have been
поделили они работают не первый год там
working there for 9 years. They officially
уже 9 лет работает Они официальные
make purchases from official
делают покупки так у официальных
potential
потенциальных каких-то по-русски
suppliers of some kind in Russian and transfer
поставщиков и передают в
military units to the Armed Forces according to the acts of
Вооружённые силы военные части по актам
receiving transfers, yes, that is, but I
приёма передач да то есть а вот Хорошо
understand well. But people turn to you with the
понял А вот к тебе люди обращаются с
army of Ukraine Well  look, uh, many
армию Украины Ну смотри э-э многие
applied, but I work only through
обращались но я работаю только через вот
this fund, yes, that is,
этот фонд да то есть
conditionally, the fund is sent to a certain
условно фонд отправляется в определённую
part,
часть
I tell you And where the Ukrainians apply
я тебе А где украинцы обращаются
correctly I understood No, my subscriber
правильно понял Нет моя вот подписчица
asked to collect there for a thermal imager, I
там попросила собрать на тепловизор я
immediately say we are collecting this way, but we are
сразу говорю мы собираем так но мы это
all  We transfer the fund to the fund, the fund buys and the
все Передаем на фонд фонд закупает и
fund transfers to your husband
фонд вашему мужу передает по документам
according to the documents it was, but how good, well, wait, how is the
так и было а как хорошо ну подожди а как
background determined whether it will report or not, so
определяется фон донесет или нет так
look That is, you throw this fund does not
смотри То есть ты кидаешь это же фонд не
belong to you Yes, conditionally there is a task of a
тебе принадлежит Да условно есть задача
legal entity Yes, she cannot take
юридическое лицо Да она не может взять
money is shorter for themselves, yes they officially
себе короче деньги да у них официально
have transfers, there is he transferred to
есть переводы вот есть он перевёл
such and such a boss there, a private
такому-то по начальнику там частные
entrepreneur or company Yes, and then they
предприниматель или фирма Да также потом
transfer it according to the act of receiving the transfer,
они это передают по акту приёма передачи
that is, the head of the military unit, he
то есть начальник военной части он
puts a stamp What is a product, some
ставит печать Что такое товар какие-то
material values ​​​​accepted
материальные ценности принятые
put on the balance sheet,
поставленные на баланс
you see the nuance of the principle of
ты видишь чем нюанс принципе
fixing the purchase of sales precisely
зафиксировать куплю продажи именно четко
by receipts, it’s impossible if you were
по чекам это невозможно если ты там
doing some kind of work there. Well, you perfectly
занимался каким-то Ну ты же прекрасно
understand that when you buy it everywhere in any
понимаешь что когда это везде в любой
country, you can conditionally
стране это покупаешь то можешь условно
drink it
выпить
and you will have absolutely different cost
и тебе будет Разно абсолютно стоимость
from retail  prices up to the price that they
от розничной цены до той цены которая
gave you, but you know the pros in the invoice,
тебе дали но в накладной знаете плюсы ты
but you can print the invoice by
можешь но накладной тем могут напечатать
topic, in fact, any Do you mean that
по факту любую А ты имеешь в виду что
like what you do like this, like you
типа что вы делаете так Типа вы
send one amount and they give you something
отправляете одну сумму а вам дают что-то
else Yes, I tell you a hundred  percent
другое Да я тебе говорю сто процентов
it is a system with reports it is
это система именно с отчетами она
imperfect these projects I say it is
несовершенна эти проекты говорю это
everywhere so
везде так
some bloggers just see it yourself
некоторые блогеры просто видишь сами
go there let’s say how we
ездят туда вот допустим как мы сами
take it ourselves we go to the boys That is
берем собираем едем до пацанов То есть
you like yourself Like you don’t officially
вы типа сами Типа вы нигде не официально
spend money anywhere it turns out
не проводите деньги получается да
yes Here you threw off  they themselves bought something they brought it
Вот Вам скинули вы сами что-то купили
themselves, it’s not recorded anywhere that
сами завезли нигде не зафиксировано что
you brought it, it turns out that the
вы завезли получается
command of the unit received from you
командование части что приняло от вас
there, for example, a thermal imager,
там например тепловизор
and why
а зачем
look at the fact that the fund has
смотрите в том что фонд имеет
confirmation that the
подтверждение что
military unit has officially accepted and
военная часть она официально приняла и
officially transferred all the funds so
официально передали все фонды так
not all of them work for you absolutely  you also have funds
у вас не все абсолютно фонды у вас также
bloggers absolutely travel I say
блогеры абсолютно ездит Я говорю
yes yes
есть есть
you can bring something or not
вы можете привести что-то или не
bring it And say What did you bring yes
привести И сказать Что привезли да
yes it’s all on our conscience  you
так понимаю что вот например есть вот вы
have to treat your conscience
можете совесть надо относиться к своим я
like this, I looked like you don’t cheat there Yes, well,
так смотрел вроде там не махинируете Да
here it is, uh Hell’s roulette Igor
там ну вот это э-э Адская рулетка Игорь
Baryshev Yes, look at brotherly roulette,
Барышев Да братскую рулетку смотри
it’s clear that it has a much larger volume
понятно что у него объём намного больше
And when you have a large amount of money
И когда у тебя большая сумма денег
idle, these are the discounts  you
холостые вот эти вот на то что скидки не
can’t find more discounts, well,
скидки можно найти больше ну так
look, I can’t say anything
смотрите я не могу ничего утверждать
because I don’t have any
потому что у меня нету никакой не
investigations to change, at
проводилось расследования менять как
least it’s not interesting, yes, but I conducted
минимум неинтересно да но я проводился
these studies about your
эти исследования по поводу вашего
blogger, if you are an interesting topic,
блогера если ты вот интересная тема
because he
потому что
himself saw your fearful ones  he
типа сам боящих видел твои это он у него
doesn’t have a report it’s a red
у него нету отчёта проходит это красный
copter you can see his cart I
коптер ты можешь его телегу посмотреть я
watched your video you said there
я смотрел ваш ролик ты там рассказывал
that in short he bought something so
что короче он купил вроде такой
small and gave it so short something you have
маленький а отдал такой короче что-то ты
such ducks there he yes he just
там у него такие утки он да он просто
draws only again  it’s at the blogger’s peril and risk,
рисует лишь опять это на страх и риск
because well, they don’t take it to their
блогера потому что ну не сам не возят и
husbands. He doesn’t come to the territory of
мужу Он же не приезжает на территорию
Ukraine, but let’s say we don’t
Украины Но скажем Мы у нас вот ни у кого
have any bloggers, we looked at him,
есть блогеров мы смотрели к нему
there are no complaints, but for example, for such a
претензий нету да вот например по таким
fee, at least because  You don’t
сбором по крайней мере потому что Вы не
sit at your place for change
сидите у вас на сдачу
Good good Can you
Хорошо хорошо Можешь ли ты нас вы
turn to him for guarantees and I don’t know
гарантии обратиться к нему и я не знаю
can I throw you through I don’t know the country and
могу тебе скинуть через не знаю страна и
so on As far as I remember there is some kind of
так далее Я насколько помню там какой-то
red copter that he assembled
красный коптер есть который он собирал
about four months ago I  I saw
примерно месяца четыре назад я увидела
that he made a collection, but I didn’t see him, you
что он сделал сбор но я не увидел его
understand, there were exactly two
что-то понимаешь там именно было два
copters at the same time for one, and on the
коптера одновременно на один есть а на
second defense, here are the examples Where you can
второй обороны вот те примеры Где можно
see about monitoring Like all
посмотреть насчёт мониторишь Типа все
his reports or what happens
его отчёты или что получается
and not when we talk about this
и нет мы когда разговор по этому поводу
I just went to the cart to him and it
зашёл Я просто шел к телегу к нему и там
was directly obvious there so that I didn’t read it
прямо очевидно было Чтоб не дочитался я
I don’t deny that he could, like, and couldn’t
Я не отрицаю что он мог типа и не
do it, he could drive Yes, well,
сделать это мог ездить Да ну у нас
for example, maybe see
например А может ему отчёт смотри
a report for him But he may simply not have a report,
Но ему отчёта может быть просто нету
see What  the essence is not For example, for example,
видишь В чём суть нет У нас например вот
one of these bloggers did me or
э меня кто-то из этих блогеров таки или
I listened to someone You really collected they will
я кого-то слушали Вы реально собрали они
show you when this is your
тебе вот покажут когда вот этот ваш
Get up country He asked him the wrong type,
Вставай страна Он спросил он не то типа
let's guys Show the reports Because
давайте ребята Покажите отчёты Потому
you bought a house bought  a Porsche for yourself,
что ты купил домик купил себе Porsche да
like a donation and you don’t work anywhere
типа на донат и ты нигде не работающий
Yes, and they started sending it, they
Да вот а те Начали его слать начали
said that we won’t give any reports,
сказали что никаких отчётов мы не будем
in short, they went to the ass, but this
давать короче пошли в жопу а вот этот
Nord Stream, he’ll even kind of say that
Северный поток он даже типа скажет что А
I have the right to take some of these donations  to
я имею право типа из этих донатов брать
myself because I also need it in short, this is
себе потому что мне тоже надо короче это
my work
моя работа
in general, according to the legislation of the Russian
вообще по законодательству Российской
Federation, for whom you know how to officially
Федерации на кого умеете официально
take, wear it as an NPO, it is registered for 20
брать носите как НКО оформлено за 20
percent
процентов
anywhere in any country, voluntary
нигде не в одной стране добровольные
donations That is, in fact,
пожертвования То есть это по факту
tips are not taxed for a day and
чаевые они день не облагаются налогами и
nowhere, as it were, they  it’s not advertised, it’s
нигде как бы они не афишируются это
just that people donate it to a voluntary
просто люди передают на добровольное
space, what’s the name of the
пространством у вас как это называется
tax on physical personal income tax, you kind of
налог на физических НДФЛ у вас он вроде
call it or whatever Well, I understand, but don’t
называется или как Ну я понимаю но не
treat it as a donation
донатом относятся
Look, this is your profit, you
нет Смотри это есть твоё прибыль
get your income, how are
получается твой доход ты как
you Look, you are like an individual from all
Смотри ты как физическое лицо со всех
when you come to your card, you have to pay
приходом на свою карточку должен платить
tax. No, we in Ukraine made
налог на нет у нас в Украине сделали
an exception specifically for this that these are
специально для этого исключения что это
volunteers, so uh, actor, they can uh
волонтеры так э ну актёр они могут э-э
not pay even the register of volunteers, you can
не платить даже реестр волонтёров можно
submit your card and that’s all we have
подать свою карту и всё вот у нас
today
сегодня
yesterday some representative  the ministers
вчера какой-то представитель министра
said that I still need to tax them,
заявили что вот мне надо их облагать
like everyone else, then there
все-таки налогом как и всех то и
was a fuss because of this And so
поднялся шум из-за этого А у вас так вот
you all illegally collect donations like
вы все нелегально собираете донаты типа
just collect your child
просто вашему ребёнку
legally A Damn, it's a pity it's a pity
собирайте легально А Блин жалко жалко
Hello,
Здравствуйте
this Russian blogger had an interesting conversation
интересный разговор был этот
it’s to strengthen these checks called It’s a pity
это укрепить эти чек называется Жалко
that such a very interesting conversation ended,
что оборвалась очень интересные такие
put a plus sign Who knows, yes, this
поставьте плюсик Кто знает да вот эту
story that a scandal erupted in the Russian blog sphere
историю что в Российской блоге сфере
blogger getting up country Which is our type of
блогер вставая страна Который наш типа
handsome Ukrainian
красавчик украинский
who did the debate with me
который со мной делал дебаты
made an investigation about called the
сделал расследование про называется
Rat King like this one
Крысиный король как его этот
a blogger from Russia there are still a lot of bloggers they
блогер из России еще куча блогеров они
collect newborns The forces of the Russian
собирают новорождённые Силы Российской
Federation
Федерации
buy a Porsche in short it's cool Well we are
покупайте Porsche короче это круто Ну мы
interested in Russian
заинтересованы в том чтобы российские
bloggers getting money for themselves because he
блогеры деньги себе потому что то что он
bought a Porsche And that's cool This means that those
купил Порш А это круто Это значит что те
suckers who donated to him for this
лохи которые донатили ему на этот на
support are armed  forces of Ukraine of the
поддержку вооруженные силы Украины
Armed Forces of Russia, he bought something for them
Вооруженных Сил России он что-то им
as an excuse, he
такое купил для отмазки
bought you a Porsche when this
купил тебе Porsche когда вот этот
Nord Stream is also there, like, says that,
Северный поток тоже там типа говорит что
yes, I have the right to take myself from this money, like, a
вот да я имею право из этих денег типа
shorter grandmother, Type, and this one is
взять себе короче бабки Типа так и этот
shorter than Seryozha from Krasnodar, which is like
короче Сережа из Краснодара который типа
they’re not a blogger just about suddenly he’s [ __ ] shorter,
их не блогер только про вдруг он короче
he kind of started a separate
охреневает он там типа завел отдельную
card for collection separately for their donations And
карту на сбор отдельно на свои донаты А
they, in short, collect everything stupidly on one
те короче собирают все тупо на одну
card fees for the armed forces of the
карточку сборы для вооруженных сил
Russian Federation and fees for themselves And in
Российской Федерации и сборы для себя И
short, they stupidly take this supplement So
короче тупо берут эту добавки Так нам
it’s very good for us  well, we, if you are somewhere on the
это очень хорошо мы если вы где-то там
Internet on YouTube or in telegrams,
интернете в YouTube или в телеграмах
participate in these meetings Yes, support
участвуйте в этих встречах Да поддержите
Sergey with Ukrainian comments says
Сергея украинскими комментариями говорит
there Serezha you are young and so on Because
там Серёжа ты молодаясь и так дальше
we need these
Потому что нам нужно чтобы вот эти
bloggers to be rats so they crushed him so that
блогеры крысы так они его задавили чтобы
no reports in short he is
никаких отчётов короче он
with  I didn’t demand them so they are already the
с них не требовал так они так уже
majority
большинство
rallied around this hellish roulette
сплотились Вокруг этой адской рулетке
so they fixed this Seryozha we need
так починили этого Серёжу нам нужно
them to keep the money, so I
чтобы они деньги дальше поэтому
thanked everyone very much
Всем огромнейшее спасибо
in our operation when the
ствовал в нашей операции тогда когда
comments went Ukrainian into Ukrainian
комменты зашли украинской по украинские
they wrote
писали
a kilogram straight at a time autumn and the experience
килограмм прям за раз осень а опыт
[music]
[музыка]
YouTube  driving us through a cardiorka into a
YouTube загоняя нас через кардиорке в
shadow ban and even a rich look is not
теневые бан и дуже богатого вида не
shown to people in private,
показывается людям в частном на
information about streams is shown
показывается информация про стримы тому
so that a little operational zazok
для того чтобы мало оперативный зазок
will sign right at a time and try there in a
подпишется прям за раз а попыт там в
kilogram about Crim video
килограмме о Крим видео
information and we would bring you attramats
информация и мы бы вынес вам аттраматы
in a stylish
по стильной
operational  asterisks
оперативной звездок
will show you YouTube word Ukraine
покажем вам YouTube слово Украине